ABDUL RASHEED RAFIAT FONT END DEVELOPER

EMAIL: raphyat97@gmail.com

BEHANCE: https://www.behance.net/raphyatrasheed

PROFILE

During my training experience at Ekobits Academy, I had practical skills with interesting technologies. I have passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach. I love to get new experiences and always learn from my surroundings and looking forward to any opportunities and challenges.

EDUCATION

2019-2020 Ekobits ICT Academy

Web Development (Diploma)

2006-2012 Ilansan senior secondary school, Jakande Estate.

> High school leaving Certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE 2020

EKOBITS ACADEMY

- > Worked with other developers to create an information website.
- I created an information website for a client

2018-TILL DATE

Freelance Makeup Artist

2014-TILL DATE

> CEO (2R)

KEY SKILLS

- Hyper Text Markup Language (HTML)
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript (JS)

HOBBIES

Reading Outdoor services Travelling

REFERENCE

Available upon request